AIDEN PATRICK WARING

GOLD COAST 4227 | 0431017997 | aiden.waring@icloud.com

OVERVIEW

Determined IT professional with a wide range of technical knowledge and support environment experience. Demonstrates unwavering commitment to service delivery and aims to deliver expert technical assistance.

Strives to play an integral role in a dedicated team. Strong personal interests in self-improvement emerging technologies and wider IT industry trends.

SKILLS & STRENGHTS

- Professional communication and strong interpersonal skills
- Positive mindset, thirst for knowledge, fast learner
- Results oriented, client focused attitude
- Proficient in delivering KPI driven results in corporate & SLA environments
- Works effectively in team environment
- Honest, compassionate, optimistic
- Flexible, highly adaptable in dynamic, fast-paced work environment

WORK EXPERIENCE

Database & IT Support Officer Maven Dental Group

May 2017 - Current

Gold Coast QLD

- Professional IT support delivery to 100+ dental practices across Australia, providing hardware, software, networking and cloud-based services.
 Supporting over 100+ locations, 2000+ devices.
- Responsible for management and delivery of business management software data replication into Data Warehouse infrastructure
- Microsoft SQL database and server management
- Server Support: Microsoft Server 2008/12/16/19, Citrix XenApp & XenDesktop
- Internal support centre management and support (Active Directory, Group Policy, Email, Windows Desktop Support, Network LAN/WAN DNS/DHCP, NAS, MFP, Firewall & VPN)
- Windows batch & PowerShell scripting, automation
- Custom application development, testing and support (.NET Development, Java, Python, Visual Basic C#)
- Analysis and reporting on network vulnerabilities to Head of IT, firewall and antivirus reporting and management
- Management of backup and disaster recovery services (Datto, MaxBackup, Shadow Protect, Veeam)
- Windows VM deployment, management (Azure, HyperV, VMWare ESXi)
- Administration of Office 365 tenancy and services (Exchange, OneDrive, PowerBI, SharePoint, Teams)

- Domain Registration, Hosting & Website Management (DNS Administration, CPanel, HTML, IIS, SSL Cert Management, WordPress)
- Mail threat protection and security application management (ATP, Mimecast)
- Custom database management, testing and support (Microsoft SQL Server, Mimer SQL, mySQL, SAP SQL Anywhere)
- Telephony support for ISDN, PABX and VoIP services (Avaya IP Office, Cisco Unified IP Systems)
- Reporting and service delivery tracking (ConnectWise, Freshdesk, PowerBI)
- Remote support of end user clients via telephone & support software (SolarWinds N-Central, Remote Desktop, TeamViewer, VPN)
- Documentation, Workflow & Process Mapping

IT Helpdesk Support Technician BITS Technology Group

August 2015 – May 2017

Gold Coast QLD

- Professional IT support delivery to managed service clients across Australia, providing hardware, software, networking and cloud-based services
- IT consultation, presale and sales delivery to reseller ISP & MSP clients
- Server Support: Microsoft Server 2008/12/16
- Telephony support for ISDN, PABX and VoIP service (Avaya IP Office)
- Remote and on-site technical support for reseller ISP & MSP clients of hardware/networking equipment (Windows Desktop Support, router, WAP, MFP)
- Website Management (DNS Administration, cPanel, HTML, WordPress)
- Administration of Office 365 tenancies (Exchange Admin)
- Remote support of MSP clients via telephone & support software (SolarWinds N-Central, Remote Desktop, TeamViewer, VPN)
- Client billing reconciliation, billing and services enquiries

EDUCATION

Griffith University – Gold Coast – Bachelor of Information Technology 2014-2016

Major: Systems Services
 Studies Include: Network Security, Database Systems and Admin, Project
 Management, Software Development

Certificate II in Creative Media Certificate I in Information Technology

2013

2013

REFERENCES

Adam Carroll

Head of IT, Maven Dental Group Level 12, 50 Cavill Ave, Surfers Paradise 4217 QLD adam.carroll@mavendental.com.au 0431733720

Kane Sajdak

Director, BITS Technology Group 4 Watts Drive, Varsity Lakes 4227 QLD kane@bitsgroup.com.au 0431733720